How exactly did Epstein operate as an
intelligence asset for the CIA, Mossad,
MI6, SBU, all of them quite honestly?
How does this work exactly? Well, if you
listen to the Zionist controlled media,
they are now bending over backwards to
paint Epstein as a Russian intelligence
asset, ignoring all of the other
connections. Here is Barry Weiss's CBS
News. Watch. Poland says it's looking
into possible connections between
convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein
and Russian intelligence services. The
announcement came after the US Justice
Department last week released millions
more files related to the federal
investigation into Epstein. Polish Prime
Minister Donald Tusk said to Tuesday,
quote, "More and more leads, more and
more information, and more and more
commentary in the global press all
relate to the suspicion that this
unprecedented pedophilia scandal was
co-organized by Russian intelligence
services about any links between."
>> By the way, by the way, I love how CBS
News, you don't even know that the
Polish the leader, I'm sorry, the the
leader is named Tusk, but okay, Tusk.
Anyway, um, how does all of how does all
this come together? John Kiyaku is a CIA
whistleblower. Of course, the Obama
administration went after him big time
and uh as he was trying to expose
everything that the Obama administration
was doing. John, welcome back to the
show. Great to see you as always.
>> Thank you. Great to see you. Thanks for
having me. Well, I want to we have a lot
to talk about here and I know Natalie
wants to unpack specifically like the
KGB side of this in a second, but I want
to first kind of start off and
understand like the mechanics if you
could maybe helping us understand how
exactly would because people are saying,
"Oh, he's MSAD or he's CIA." And I think
you have said to us in the past that
he's probably just an asset associated
or in alignment with them. How does how
exactly does that work? How exactly did
it work for him, do you believe? Well,
I've been I'm proud to say I've been
consistent that from the beginning I
said that I thought he was what was
called an access agent most likely for
the Mossad. An access agent is somebody
who can give you access to people that
you're really interested in. It's not
necessarily going to be Jeffrey Epstein
that has access to classified uh
information, but Peter Mandlesson
certainly does and Bill Clinton does and
the former Prince Andrew certainly did.
and maybe you get some business uh
information, business secrets or
economic secrets from the likes of Bill
Gates. So, I think that Jeffrey Epstein
was was probably recruited by the
Israelis to provide access to the
targets that the Israelis were really
interested in. But with that said, an
access agent is somebody who also can
still be a free agent. And so if the FBI
has a question and maybe you can you can
establish a quidd proquo with the FBI,
maybe you answer the FBI's question or
the CIA or the MI6 or MI5 or the French
or whomever because you want to bank
those uh those favors and uh maybe have
some goodwill down the line in case you
get jammed up. He got jammed up and he
didn't have anybody to help him. Can I
just follow up on that real quick? Which
is one of the big questions that
Congressman Thomas Massie wanted. He he
he told me earlier in the week he said
that among the missing things that they
demanded as part of the Epstein
transparency act was the name of the
person or persons who were responsible
for giving him such a lenient sentence
in 2007208.
Would that be intelligence related? Do
you believe?
>> I think it's 100% intelligence related.
Alex Aosta has said, Alex Aosta, the
former uh secretary of labor, who at the
time was the US attorney who prosecuted
Jeffrey Epstein, said that uh the order
to give Epstein a sweetheart sentence
came from the top. And when asked why,
all he said was intelligence. So make of
that what you will. But then you have to
think, who has authority over a US
attorney? Well, frankly, the only person
who has authority, direct authority over
a US attorney is uh is the attorney
general. At the time, that was um
Alberto Gonzalez. Alberto Gonzalez,
God bless him, was a lightweight. It
wasn't up to Alberto Gonzalez. So, who
was above Alberto Gonzalez? It was the
president and the vice president. So,
what do we make of that? Was it George
W. Bush that ordered this? If so, why?
Was it Dick Cheney? If so, why? But I
think we have a right to know. What if
that sore throat or fever that hit you
overnight didn't actually have to cancel
your family trip or miss work or waste
hours at an urgent care? Instead, you
could actually just open your medical
emergency kit from the wellness company,
match your symptoms to the doctor
recommended guide, and then start
treatment immediately right in your
house. This is not a first aid kit. It's
a mini urgent care right at your
fingertips. Inside you're going to find
eight core prescriptions to treat over
30 conditions like COVID, strep throat,
pneumonia, urinary tract infections, and
more. No more waiting rooms, no more
pharmacy lines. Modernized medicine
right when you need it. We have one
right upstairs in our own medicine
cabinet. And ordering it is simple. At
checkout, simply complete a short intake
form and a licensed doctor will review,
fill your scripts, and preventative
peace of mind arrives at your home in
one week. No one wants to be sick during
the holidays or any other time. So, be
prepared. Save yourself time and money.
The medical emergency kit puts urgent
care in your hands anytime you need it.
So, go to twwc.health/redacted
right now and use that code redacted to
save a nice discount and free shipping.
Again, tw.alth/redacted.
>> What do you make of this media narrative
that oh, definitely he's KGB? I mean,
set aside the fact that the KGB has been
dissolved since the '9s and Epstein was
doing most of his work in the 2000s. Uh,
the way Daryl Cooper explained it on
Tucker Tucker Carlson I I thought was
great because he could move between
governments if if Mossad That's right.
You know, wanted an introduction to
somebody in the KGB. Then you have these
shadow actors that can act as a liaison.
That's what uh Robert Maxwell in fact
did.
>> That's right. So, can you extrapolate on
that role and are there people still
doing it?
>> Oh, I think that is exactly correct. I
think that that he really has has nailed
it. You know, the Israelis I'm I'm going
to get threats from the Israelis again.
Every time I say something like this, I
get threats, but I'm going to say it
again anyway. The Israelis are free
agents. The Israelis are not necessarily
our friends. they are when it suits
them. But when it suits them to be
friendly with the Russians, they go with
the Russians or with the Chinese or the
Germans or, you know, anybody. It
doesn't make any difference. The
Israelis do what's best for the
Israelis. And if that means using a a
source like like Jeffrey Epstein and and
passing information on to a hostile
intelligence service, or at least one
that's hostile to the United States,
that's exactly what they're going to do.
I got into a spirited debate with Alan
Dersowitz about this on the Pierce
Morgan show a few weeks ago and I
thought the man was going to have a
stroke when I said that Jeffrey Epstein
was most likely working on behalf of the
Israelis. And then he said something
that was completely backward. He said
that he had been Epstein's uh attorney
and if Epstein had been working for the
Israelis he would have told Durowitz and
Dersuits would have used that
information to get Epstein an even
lighter sentence. And I said, "Wait a
minute, professor.
If you're saying that you would have
gone to the White House to say, "My
client is committing espionage for the
Israeli government," you think that
would have gotten him a lighter
sentence? I think he would have been
hanging from a tree,
>> right? Gone from there.
>> Yeah. He would have been put in prison
for the rest of his life or put to
death.
>> Exactly.
>> Well, that's how it's supposed to work.
We're we're seeing that it doesn't right
now. you can meet with former Israeli or
former US traders and
>> yeah Jonathan Pard well Jonathan Pard
got he did every day of his 30 years of
course he's you know he's a hero in
Israel now and he's running for the
Knesset but but he did every single day
of his 30 years
>> oh good point good point
>> now and then now he gets to hang out
with Ambassador Mike Huckabe who is
apparently friends with him so that's
how it works
>> VIP treatment in the American embassy
>> unbelievable um so the mechanics of this
I'm just still trying to wrap my head
around like
Jeffrey Epstein's just like sitting
there in his in his sex layer or
whatever and he just like gets a, you
know, gets some like a phone call. He
gets like a pager. Come meet me in the
park. We want you to do this. You know,
shake shake this hand cuz the other hand
is shaking it back. Like what does that
look like for somebody like Jeffrey
Epstein?
>> Well, if Jeffrey Epste were treated as a
normal source, then the answer is yes.
You get a you get a phone call saying,
"Hey, how was how's your mom doing?" And
the answer is, "My mom is feeling much
better. Thank you." And that means,
"Meet me at the parking lot of the yacht
club at 2:00 in the morning. You You
have this all set up in advance." And
then he goes and uh and does his meeting
and gets his marching orders.
>> And so there wouldn't be an email trail
here, right, John? I guess that's
>> Oh, no, no, no. There would never be an
email trail. This is all done verbally
or just using signals. You remember
during uh during Watergate, uh
would would uh react to Bob
Woodward putting an American flag in a
flower pot on his apartment balcony.
That triggered a meeting that night at
9:00 in a parking garage in Rosland, the
Rosland neighborhood of Arlington,
Virginia. So, all of this is always set
up in advance. So, you never have to
actually put anything in writing or say,
"Meet me at 8:00."
>> So, okay, that is covert. It's done by
Signals, but all the sex stuff was overt
and written out and in writing. So,
okay.
>> Yeah, good point.
>> Explain that to me and then can you
please or just take an opinion because I
don't think you're doing that. I don't
think you can personally explain it. And
then also, I would like to know how you
think this
>> international spy espionage relates to
this demonic sex predator. Are they
related or is it just that one allowed
the other or did one actually give
leverage for the other because or are
they unrelated?
>> Yeah. No, that that's a great question
and a very important one and I think
that they were two issues running
parallel with one another. I think that
the Israelis or whomever uh was the
recruiter of Jeffrey Epstein said this
guy has a major vulnerability and his
vulnerability is that he's a pedophile.
Uh we can use that to our advantage. He
can get us information. We'll continue
to supply him with money. uh and we'll
just turn a blind eye to his pedophilia.
So they they were able to identify that
vulnerability, that hook in order to to
hook him and reel him in. And then they
just let him do his thing with with
girls and uh and uh important world
leaders and just let the cards fall
where they fell.
>> How much of it do you think was a
honeypot operation?
You know, I think it probably became a
honeypot operation. You know, I'm I'm
wondering, you you have to figure this
was going on for decades. And I'm
wondering if if any intelligence
service, even one as good as the
Israelis, was able to see so far in
advance that they could turn this into a
honeypot. I mean, of course, it's it's
obvious by the late 1990s or the early
2000s that's exactly what it is. that
you can entrap as many of of these
movers and shakers as you possibly want
to. Look at Peter Mandelon. You know,
I've been thinking about this all day
today. Peter Mandlesson, the former
British ambassador to the United States,
the the the member until earlier this
week of the h the House of Lords.
He's in so deep now after lying and
lying and lying that he barely knew
Jeffrey Epstein. He's in so deep that
this risks collapsing the British
government. There were calls by members
of the Labor Party today for the Labor
Prime Minister Kier Starmer to resign
because he had been so easily duped by
Peter Mandlesson. So the stakes are very
very high here. This is really serious.
>> Giving him state secrets. Yeah.
Funneling state secrets to Jeffrey
Epstein. Like I mean that's treason. I
don't know how he avoids prison at this
point. I mean, I
>> and and the laws the state uh the state
secrecy act law in the UK is far far
tougher than the espionage act is here
in the United States.
>> Wow.
>> Peter Manosen could find himself
spending the rest of his natural life in
prison.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> I guess John, we'll get you out of here
on that. I'm just curious from your
perspective, having worked at the CIA,
blowing the whistle at the CIA, when
you're seeing all these documents and
you're a guest on our show and we're
specifically talking about the
intelligence side. Is there something
you think that like people are missing
that people haven't looked at more
closely? Something that's been like
keeping you up at night or ringing your
hands that you think people need to pay
attention to?
>> You know, one of one of the things that
bothers me very much is that the more
important people become in their lives,
the more we as a society are willing to
cut them slack.
>> And we shouldn't do that. People are
people and people are sexual beings. God
knows what's in their hearts. God knows
what they do behind closed doors. And so
nobody should be given the benefit of
the doubt in crimes where children are
the victims.
>> Right. I I just got upset because Roger
Stone was on the show and he said
absolutely Trump didn't do anything and
I said, "Well, these documents, you
know, are not favorable. Did somebody
look into them?" because I don't have
any kind of preconceived notion whether
Trump is innocent or guilty. I would
like to see proof. I would like to see
them be transparent with us. And now
that we have more allegations, a valid
question is anybody follow up on that?
Is there any anything there? Anybody
new?
>> Right. And so far how so I I I take your
answer to be nobody is above scrutiny
especially because our jobs as the
adults of the world is to protect
children.
>> That is it right there. I have five
children of my own and if this had
happened to one of them, I'm not sure I
could control myself.
>> John Wick level. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> John Wick.
>> I mean I mean guess we What about Trump?
I mean there's a lot of going back and
forth here on this, right? Um, you have
>> Yeah. You know, if if I were Donald
Trump and I were confident in my
innocence, I would just release
everything.
>> Just release it.
>> Yeah. Release it and put it to bed.
>> Alex Jones was saying, you know, he was
saying, look, the the big the big rub
here for Trump is that he waited so long
to release it. And that if if he if he
releases everything that he'll be
absolved of everything.
>> So, if that's the case, then release it
all. Why are you continue to insult
insult reporters like Caitlyn? I mean, I
don't have any love for whatever any of
these reporters from CNN, but like like
just release everything then so no one
has to ask any questions. Like what is
there to hide? If you're so innocent,
release everything.
>> That's exactly right. I I just don't
understand why it has taken this long
and it's not even done yet.
>> Right.
>> No, he's shooting himself in the foot if
he's truly truly truly innocent.
>> Well, John, it's so good to talk to you.
You run cover for nobody.
>> Pleasure.
>> Yeah. No.
>> Yeah. We don't do that.
>> The show. Thanks for having me. We love
you.
>> Thank you, John. Always great to uh
John, tell people where people can find
Tell people where people can find your
show.
>> Oh, thanks. I've got three actually.
I've got uh Deep Program every day
Monday through Friday at 9:00 a.m. on
both YouTube and Rumble. I have Deep
Focus, which drops uh twice a week on
YouTube. And on Apple Podcasts, I have
John Kiryaku's Dead Drop, What Makes a
Spy Tick. [snorts]
>> All right,
>> John. Great to see you as always. Thanks
so much for taking time.
>> Pleasure. Thanks. Thank you.